MATTHEW JONES

UI / UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

M S C O T T J O N E S . C O

CONTACT



770 560 5712



MATT@MSCOTTJONES.CO



195 ARIZONA AVE, NE, UNIT 178 ATLANTA, GA. 30307

ABOUT

A curious problem solver by nature, a designer and developer by trade. I am a creative professional with a knack for code and bringing a high touch aesthetic to any project. I am of a mind that constantly learns and grows with my industry.

When I'm not working on learning more about development technologies and techniques or researching new designs, I keep my body moving. Staying fit and educating myself about nutrition are some of my favorite past times.

LINKS



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/MATTJONESATL/



TWITTER.COM/MATHIEU_JONES

EXPERTISE

TOOLS









SKILLS

- Responsive Design
- UI / UX Design
- Print & Layout Design
- · Semantic Coding

LANGUAGES

- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript

IDEs

- Brackets
- · Sublime Text

Bootstrap

· Coding for Email

· Mac OS Support

FRAMEWORKS

· Photography

· Client-Designer Relations

¡Query

CMSs

- WordPress
- Sitefinity

EMAIL TOOLS

- Silverpop
- Exact Target

EXPERIENCE

Oct 2013 - Present

METRO ATLANTA CHAMBER

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

- Supported and provided design expertise to the ChooseATL campaign
- · Directly supported the president for design needs
- · Improved and maintained code for email campaigns to member database
- · Edited, launched and maintained website code
- · Headed design concepts for high profile events
- Lead design of print, digital and staging of company's Annual Meeting
- Created and maintained the project management system and file server
- · Helped to support and maintain the company's website
- · Contributed to the company's social media strategy

Mar 2013 - Sept 2013

CITY OF ATLANTA, PARKS & RECREATION

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER & SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

- Headed design and development of print materials
- Supported the Mayor of Atlanta in the Centers of Hope initiative
- Supported the Department of Cultural Affairs
- · Created the department's social media strategy
- · Launched a blog using the Tumblr platform
- · Improved and maintained website content
- · Provided photography services

Oct 2009 - Mar 2013

METRO ATLANTA CHAMBER

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & PHOTOGRAPHER

- · Headed design needs for the Chick-fil-A Bowl account
- Provided photography services for events and managed project files
- · Lead design of materials for internal and external use

EDUCATION

Sept 2014 - Dec 2014

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM

Aug 2004 - Aug 2008

GEORGIA SOUTHERN UNIVERSITY

BFA WITH A CONCENTRATION IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Mar 2015

SPEAKEASY

"TALK SO PEOPLE WILL LISTEN" PUBLIC SPEAKING PROGRAM

ART INSTITUTE OF ATLANTA

FOUR WEEK PHOTOGRAPHY WORKSHOP

ORGANIZATIONS

- AIGA Atlanta
- General Assembly Alumni
- · Atlanta Web Design Group (AWDG)
- · Atlanta Startup Village
- · Atlanta Wordpress & SEO